netbet.org 2019-02-03

# Privacy Policy

We at https://www.netbet.org care about your privacy. Please, read this Privacy Policy carefully to know our approach towards the use of your personal information. If we ask you to give certain data that can help us to identify you when using this website, you can be sure that this information will only be used in compliance with our privacy statement.

Netbet.org may change this policy when updating this page. Check our Privacy Policy page from time to time to be aware of the changes.

 **Collecting and Using Information:**

  * When registering with Netbet.org, when visiting our partners’ pages, and when entering our promotions.
  * When registering you have to give us the following personal data: name, email address, gender, birth date, address, occupation, and hobbies.
  * Netbet.org server logs automatically record your IP address, and page request.
  * The general purposes we collect the information are to know your demand for gambling products and services, to advertise the content given to you, to make our services better, contact you, and research purposes.
  * We do not offer products and services for children under 18. So they can’t register at Netbet.org.

 **Disclosure and Sharing of Information:**

We will not share or sell your personal data to third party, except when you request a product or service from us, with your permission, or when:

  * Netbet.org has to answer to subpoenas, court orders, legal processes, every time we need to defend ourselves against legal claims, or exercise our legal rights;
  * It’s necessary to share information for prevention, investigation, or taking actions concerning illegal activities, violations of our terms of use, or as required by law.
  * Netbet.org shares information in case of our company’s merger with another company. In this case you will be notified before transferring your personal information.
  * You will be able to send a request for your account deactivation or closure any time you wish.

 **Security Policy:**

  * Only the staff members can access your personal data in order to carry out their duties and/or provide services and products.
  * We guaranty that your personal data is protected by physical, and electronic.
  * Netbet.org uses SSL encryption for your data protection.
  * There is password protection for your account information.

 **Privacy Policy Changes:**

  * Netbet.org policy is subject to change and update. In case of any important changes concerning personal information treatment, we will notify you by an email.

For all questions, suggestions, or comments, feel free to contact us **here**.
